Papers of Diane Wakoski circa 1959-1980 (bulk 1959-1978)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Papers of Diane Wakoski 1959-1980(bulk 1959-1978)
MS 149
Wakoski, Diane-
Diane Wakoski Papers document the literary life of the American poet Diane Wakoski. The collection contains manuscripts, chapbooks, reviews, interviews, proofs, copies of books and correspondence.
41 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
Diane Wakoski is an American poet who is associated with the deep image poets as well as the confessional and Beat poets of the 1960s. She was born on August 3rd, 1937 in Whittier, California. Wakoski received her bachelor's degree in English from the University of California at Berkeley, where she studied with Thom Gunn, Josephine Miles, and Tom Parkinson.
After receiving her Bachelor’s Degree, Wakoski moved to New York City where she participated in the thriving poetry scene in Manhattan’s Lower East Side. During this time she produced work that appeared in several chapbooks and journal collections of poetry. In 1976 she moved to East Lansing, Michigan, and taught at Michigan State University.
Much of her poetry focuses on the relationship between men and women, and includes conversations with larger than life historical figures such as George Washington, the Buddha, and the King of Spain.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 4 series (arrangement varies by series)
Series I: Correspondence 1968-1978
Series II: Books and Chapbooks 1962-1978
Series III:Broadsides 1971-1975
Series IV: Periodicals 1971-1975
Series V: Tony Weinberger 1971, undated
Series VI: Correspondence, additional records 1960-1980
Series VII: Published Materials, additional records 1960-1980
Series VIII: Manuscripts, additional records 1960-1980
Series IX: Works by Others, additional records 1960-1980
Series X: Miscellaneous, additional records
Sereis XI: Personal Journals, additional records 1966-1984
Series XII: Chapbooks and journals, additional records 1955-1978
Scope and Content Note
Collection includes manuscripts, chapbooks, reviews, interviews, proofs and copies of books. Some are signed; many are published by Black Sparrow Press of Los Angeles. Much of the correspondence is from Wakoski to John Martin, of Black Sparrow Press. Some is to Martin from Tony Weinberger, who has published and unpublished material in this collection. Also present are little magazines, two recordings of Wakoski's readings, broadsides, postcards, and posters; many signed by her.
The addendum to the collection, added in 2013, contains primarily correspondence between Wakoski and various authors, intellectuals, editors and fans, a bulk of it between the years of 1960-1975. Also included in the addendum is later work, loose and unpublished poetry, collaborative works, and later works found in chapbooks and small journals from 1965-1975. This addendum has a structure that varies from the original collection and contains mostly personal works.
Related materials pertaining to Diane Wkoski may be found at Michigan State University Libraries, Special Collections as part of the Michigan Writers Collection.
Access Terms
Wakoski, Diane--Archives.
Black Sparrow Press.
Perishable Press
American poetry--20th century.
Women poets, American--20th century.
Small press books--Specimens.
Little magazines--Specimens.
Container List
- Correspondence, 1968-
  - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ray Freed, Doctor Generosity's Almanac, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tony Weinberger Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tony Weinberger Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tony Weinberger Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript; "The Pepper Plant", 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript, "The Fable of the Lion and the Scorpion", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence realting to Diane Wakoski's work (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Books and Chapbooks, 1959-
  - Justice is Reason Enough, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Coins & Coffins, Hawk's Well Press, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Discrepancies and Apparitions, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hardcover, "Discrepancies and Apparitions", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Proofs, "Discrepencies and Apparitions", Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Original holograph manuscript, "The George Washington Poems", 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ex-library Copy, with original wrappers, "The George Washington Poems", Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wrappers, "The George Washingon Poems", Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Wrappers, "The George Washington Poems", 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - As above, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, order forms, "Greed, Parts One and Two", 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Greed, Parts 1 and 2 wrappers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hardcover, "Greed, Parts One and Two", Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Diamond Merchant, The Sans Souci Press, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Inside the Blood Factory wrappers, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Inside the Blood Factory Hardcover, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Inside the Blood Factory Hardcover, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Inside the Blood Factory Hardcover, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Inside the Blood Factory Flyer, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Thanking my Mother for Piano Lessons, wrappers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Thanking my Mother for Piano Lessons, wrappers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Lament of the Lady Bank Dick Hardcover, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Lament of the Lady Bank Dick Hardcover, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Lament of the Lady Bank Dick Hardcover, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Lament of the Lady Bank Dick, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Greed, Parts 3 and 4 wrappers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Greed, Parts 3 and 4, wrappers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Greed, Parts 3 and 4, Handbound in Boards, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Moon Has a Complicated Geography, wrappers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Black Dream Ditty for Billy "The Kid" M Seen in Dr. Generosity's Bar Recruiting for Hell's Angels and Black Mafia, wrappers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Black Dream Ditty for Billy "The Kid's" M Seen in Dr. Generosity's Bar Recruiting for Hell's Angels and Black Mafia, hardcover, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Magellanic Clouds, wrappers, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Magellanic Clouds, hardcover, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Magellanic Clouds, flyer, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - On Barbara's Shore wrappers, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - On Barbara's Shore hardcover, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Greed, wrappers, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Greed, hardcover, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Greed, handbound in boards, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Greed flyer, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - The Water Element Song for Sylvia, typed and photocopied, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Water Element Song for Sylvia, advance uncorrected proof, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Water Element Song for Sylvia, wrappers, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems, hardcover, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems, hardcover, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems publication day party invitation, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Smudging wrappers, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Smudging hardcover, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Smudging handbound in boards, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Smudging flyers, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pumpkin Pie or, Reassurance are Always False, Tho we Love them. Only Physics Counts first issue, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pumpkin Pie or, Reassurances are Always False, Tho We Love Them. Only Physics counts Handbound, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Form is an Extension of the Content, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sparrow 1-2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Greed/Parts 8, 9, 11 wrappers, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Greed/Parts 8, 9, 11 hardcover, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Greed/Parts 8, 9, 11, handbound in boards, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Greed/Parts 8, 9, 11, flyers, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dancing on the Grave of a Son of a Bitch, wrappers, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dancing on the Grave of a Son of a Bitch, hardcover, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dancing on the Grave of a Son of a Bitch, handbound, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Winter Sequences, broadside, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Trilogy, wrappers, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Trilogy, hardcover, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Looking for the King of Spain, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wandering Tattle, unsewn proof, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Wandering Tattle, blue leather spine, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Wandering Tattle, green leather spine, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Wandering Tattle, blue leather spine, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wandering Tattle, blue leather spine, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Abalone wrappers, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Abalone handbound, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Creating a Personal Mythology, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Fable of the Lion and the Scorpion, Wrappers, Pentagram Press, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, uncorrected proof, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, wrappers, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, hardcover, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, flyer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Five Poems, c. 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Laguna Contract, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - George Washington's Camp Cups, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Variations on a Theme (an Essay on Revision), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Variations on a Theme (an Essay on Revision), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Waiting for the King of Spain, wrappers, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Waiting for the King of Spain, hardcover, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Waiting for the King of Spain, hardcover, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Waiting for the King of Spain, handbound, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Ring, hardcover, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Ring, hardcover, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Ring, handbound, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Overnight Project with Wood, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Spending Christmas with the Man From Receiving at Sears, wrappers, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, handbound, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, handbound, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Man Who Shook Hands, uncorrected proof, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Man Who Shook Hands, wrappers, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Man Who Shook Hands, hardcover, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The Man Who Shook Hands, review, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Manuscripts, "Monday through Friday" and "Anger at the Weather", 1965 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Reviews by Diane Wakoski, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Interviews with Diane Wakoski, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Recordings (45 RPM), "The Magellanic Clouds" New York, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tape, recorded live 12/2/1970 at Intersection, San Francisco (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Resume and Photograph, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations by Diane Wakoski, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Diary/Workbook, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Series III: Broadsides, 1970-1975
  - Holograph Poem, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Broadsides/Postcards, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Portfolio, Diane Wakoski, 2 Broadsides, 3 Postcards, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Some Brilliant Sky; Music by Marc Baranchik to a Test by Diane Wakoski, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Flyers/Posters, 1966-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Love Your Big Fat Snail" The Tenth Muse, San Francisco, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Periodicals, 1961-1975
  - Seventh Street: An Anthology of Poems from Les Deux Megots, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trobar 3, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Trobar 4, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nomad/New York nos 10-11, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Four Young Lady Poets, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Poems From the Floating World v. 4, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Poems From the Floating World v. 4, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Outside v. 1 no. 3, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Judson Review v. 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Carlton Miscellany v. 4 no. 4, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Set. No. 2, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Hardward Poets Occasional no. 3, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - El Cornor Emplumado, no 11, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hardware Poet's Occasional no. 4, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pogamoggan no. 1, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Pogamoggan no. 1, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Dream Sheet, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Island no. 3, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Ante v. 1 no. 1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Some/Thing v. 1 no. 3, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Now Now, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Some/Thing v. 1 no. 2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Software no. 1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Software no. 2, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - El Corno Emplumado no 17, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Io no. 2, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Art and Literature no. 9, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Interepid v. 1, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ante v. 2 no. 1, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Io no. 3, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Athanor v. 1 no. 1, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Poetmeat no. 13, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Haravec no. 3, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - El Corno Emplumado no. 24, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Analecta no. 1, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The East Side Scene, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Minnesota Review v. 8 no. 2, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Odda Tala no. 2, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Revita de Bellas Artes no. 23, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - A Play and Two Poems, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Statement, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Maps, no 3, c. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Caterpillar (no. 6) v. 2, no. 1, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sumac v. 1, no. 3, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Caterpillar (no. 7) v. 2, no. 2, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Occident v. 3, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mad Windows, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - New American Review no. 7, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lillabulero no. 7, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Renew Jerusalem, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Caterpillar (nos 8-9) v. 2 no. 3-4, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sumac v. 2 no. 1, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sumac, v. 2 no. 2-3, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Antioch Review v. 30, no. 1, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Jeopardy, v. 6, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Shaded Room no. 1, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Caterpillar v. 3 no. 2, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Spectrum v. 5 no. 3, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Far Point no. 4, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Tuatera no. 2, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hearse no. 12, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Emily Dickinson: Letters from the World, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kayak no. 21, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Armadillo no 2, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Doctor's Generosity Almanac: 17 Poets, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Friendly Local Press v. 1 no. 6, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Inside Outer Space; New Poems of the Space Age, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hearse no. 13, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The Book Review, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Desert Review, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Lillabulero, no. 9, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Lillabulero, no. 8, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The New York Quarterly no. 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Caterpillar (no 14), v. 4, n. 2, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Poetry v. 117, no. 6, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Falcon nos 2-3, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Crazy Horse no. 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Unmuzzled Ox, v. 1, no. 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - A Caterpillar Anthology, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Works v. 3, no. 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Caterpillar (no. 17) v.5, no. 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Mediterranean Review v. 1, no. 2, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Lemming, no. 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Wrappers in Mailing envelope, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Handbound, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Falcons, no. 4, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Caterpillar (no 18), v. 5, no.2, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ironwood, no. 1, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Kayak, no. 28, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Equal Time, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Aggressive Ways of the Casual Stranger, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Open Reading no. 2, Transformations (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Parnassus: Poetry in Review, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Arion's Dolphin Winter, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Amaranthus, no. 7, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Tens, no. 4, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The Poetry Miscellany, v. 2, no. 1, 1972-73 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Vort, no. 3, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Poetry, v. 122, no. 4, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Shake the Kaleidoscope: A new Anthology of Modern Poetry, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Loves, Etc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Poetry In America, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Green Wrappers, signed, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Blue Wrappers, signed, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Handbound, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Contemporary Scene, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Preferences; 51 American Poets Choose Poems from Their Own Work and From the Past, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 7 Poets 7 Poems, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lakes&Prairies, v. 1, no. 1, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lakes&Prairies, v. 1, no. 1, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Craft of Poetry: Interviews from the New Work Quarterly, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ironwood no. 5, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Burning Deck Postcards: The First Ten, c. 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Burning Deck Postcards: The Second Ten, c. 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Burning Deck Postcards: The Third Ten, c. 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Wrappers, "The Last Poem by Diane Wakoski & Touch Company by Charles Bukowski, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Handbound in boards, "The Last Poem by Diane Wakoski & Tough Company by Charles Bukowski, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - A Checklist of the First One Hundred Publications of the Black Sparrow Press, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, Black Sparrow Press, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 17, no. 11, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 1, no. 1, November-December 1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 2, no 1, January-February, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v.2, no. 2, March-April, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 2, no. 3, May-June, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 2, no. 4, July-August, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 2, no. 5, September-October, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 2, no. 6, November-December, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 3, no. 1, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The New York Reivew of Books, v. 3, no. 2, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Series V: Tony Weinberger, 1971, undated
  - Max's Kansas City Stories, by Tony Weinberger, wrappers, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Max's Kansas City Stories, by Tony Weinberger, hardcover, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Some Notes on the Max's Kansas City Stories, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reviews of Max's Kansas City Stories, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Walking Stick, by Tony Weinberger, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Series VI: Correspondence, additional records, 1960-1980
  - A, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Aaron, Jonathan, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Abbey, Edward, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Ward, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Abrams, Sam and Barbara, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Alder Publishing, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Academy of American Poets, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ackerman, Richard C., undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Agnes, Sister, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Agha Shaid, Ali, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Alaska, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Alber, Richard E. (Dick), undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Albright College, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Aleneir, Karen, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Alexander, Paul, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Allen, Dick, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Alexander, D., undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Allman, Barb, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Altizer, Neil, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - The American Book Review, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - American Literacy Anthology, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - The American Poetry Review, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - The American Poetry Review: DW Column, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The American Poetry Review: DW Column, fan letters, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - American Program Bureau, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Ammons, A.R. (Archie), undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Amster, Jayson, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Anania, Michael, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Carolyn, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, David, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Jack, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Jane, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Jessica, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Leonora, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Anderson, Marta, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Anderson, Mavourneen (Mrs. John), undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Andre, Michael, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Anfinson, Barbara, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Anthologies, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Anton, David and Eleanor, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Antioch, Columbia, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Appel, Ellen, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Applebaum, Arthur, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Appleman, Phil, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Arizona Poetry Society, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Arizona State University Library, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Armstrong, Sara, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Arteseros, Sally, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Ashbaugh, Gwendolyn, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Astrologers Gild, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Astrology, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Athanson, Arthur, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - The Atlantic Monthly Press, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Atwood, Margaret, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Audi, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Audobon Convention, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Augustine, Jane, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The Author’s Guild/League of General Information, August-December 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Author’s Guild/ League of General Information, January 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Author Lecture Service of Doubleday and Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - The Author’s Guild, Inc/ The Author’s League of America, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - The Author’s League/ League: Author Information, Organizational Information, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The Author’s Guild/ League of General Information, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Awards and Contests, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Axelrod, David, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - B, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Bahamas, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Bakken, Dick, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Balmer, Helen, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Banks, Nancy, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Barclay, Ann, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Barbarian Press, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Barlin, Beverly, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Barsam, Richard, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bartlet, Lee, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Bay Arts Writer’s Guild, Escanaba, Michigan, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Beacham, Walton, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Beaulire, Les, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Bedigiam, Dorothea, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Bell, Lindolf, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)